Mom, can I watch Chrysalis's live stream
while I eat my McDonald's?
>> Sure, sweetie, but not for long. We're
going to be at the Japanese bath house
in 5 minutes.
Okay, let me explain what happened. All
right, I was surfing a site. Okay, the
[__] got downloaded. Like, I didn't
trigger an effing download. It just got
downloaded. I opened up the effing text
document. I saw what was in it. I
deleted the text document. I deleted it.
But the problem with Windows 11 is that
even if you delete the text document, it
apparently still stays there. So, it was
still there after I deleted it. I've
told you guys a thousand times that's
what happened. I I I Dude, I'm sorry.
Like, I have like 3 terb of hentai on my
hard drive, bro. Like, like a lot.
Sometimes you go to a site and some [__]
downloads on your [__] You don't want
it. You delete it. And that like that's
just what happened, man. Okay. That's
what happened. I'm sorry. All right.
Like, I don't know how many times I have
to explain this, but that's what
happened. Dude, let's just move on,
please. No one's going to believe me,
man.
>> Okay. What's your problem?
>> Nothing.
>> That's a lie. You've been acting like a
huge [__] since we left the McDonald's
drive-thru.
>> Oh,
>> you want to know why Trixie is mad?
>> Not if you're going to hit me.
>> Trixie is angry because she couldn't
afford this trip for you, Sparkle.
Trixie works two jobs, Twilight, too.
And you still had to ask Celestia to pay
for it.
>> You are acting so gay. If anything, I
should be the one mad at you. But I'm
not because it's Valentine's Day, which
is about celebrating love and all that
[__] Besides, it is imperative that we
go through with this because you smell
like [__]
>> She Twilight Sparkle Chen, would you
like some of my dectable orange chicken?
>> Oh, hell no. Fluttershy, what are you
doing here?
>> This is the place of my people,
Twilight, because I'm Chinese.
Fluttershy, we went over this many times
before. Being yellow doesn't make you a
Chinese lady who got smuggled here as a
baby from mainland China. You are an
ugly halflinger horse from the magical
land of Ponyville.
>> Is that so? Then what have you say about
this?
>> That's a picture of the great wave off
Kanagawa by Katsushika Hokasai that you
photoshopped yourself into. Also, that's
not Chinese.
Wow, your hat is really cool. Stop it.
You're encouraging her wrongness.
>> You can have it. I have 20 more back in
my room because I am in fact Chinese.
>> Moms, look, it's my acquaintances from
school who mildly tolerate me. Can I go
say hi before they see me and run?
>> You're a grown ass woman. You don't need
to ask for permission. She still hasn't
shaved her armpits. Twilight, I think
our daughter is autistic.
>> Don't call her that. Being autistic is
weird and wrong.
>> You going to tell me what to do now,
huh? I'll call her what I want as a mega
popular magician. Three people came to
your last show.
>> What? What did you just say?
>> What I mean to say is your hobby doesn't
exactly make bread if I'm being
perfectly honest.
>> Hobby?
You think I'm a loser? A loser with a
fat ass. Well, at least I'm not some
nerd that goes begging their elementary
school teacher for money.
>> Well, maybe I wouldn't have to beg for
money if you stopped with your greatest
trick of all. Making all our money
disappear buying those stinking games on
the XStation. It's called the Xbox, you
swine. And I used to play a lot more
games before I married you.
>> What is that supposed to mean?
>> It means Trixie is going to take a
massive [__] with the fury of a scorned
diva. And it must not be delayed, for
she has much to think about.
>> This Valentine's Day sucks balls.
>> Yeah, I wanted to spend it with Asian
people. And you're purple,
>> my friends.
>> Oh, hey, it's fuzzy armpit girl. Hey,
Flawless. I heard your mom say you were
on the autism spectrum. That's so sad.
Is that why you stim so much?
>> Sometimes Granny Smith lures ponies
behind the barn and we never see them
again. What are you expecting us to do
with that information? I just felt like
getting the word out some pony might do
something. Well, we aren't.
>> Oh my god. Are you kidding me? A short
bus is pulling up. That's like so gross.
Hi. Can we park next to you?
>> Sure. Thanks for asking. I'm pretty bad
at socializing, so it's good when ponies
are direct.
>> In case anyone was wondering,
>> those flowers over there are real
beautiful.
>> Uh, can you shut up, you freak? I was
literally talking. You're almost as bad
as Flawless and her disgusting hairy
armpits and the changeling girl because
she's black. What were you saying?
>> Oh, yeah. I just wanted to say that I of
course got a queen sweep because I'm
rich as hell. I hear sweetie Bell is
also here, but won't leave her room
because it's the cheapest at the bath
house. So, she's going to spend the
weekend eating peanut butter and jelly
sandwiches. But like without the peanut
butter because Rarity is poor and can't
afford it. It's so funny. I'm going back
to my room to eat sushi. Scootaloo and
Apple Bloom. You can come watch because
you're not ugly freaks. Oh, and
flawless. The Phoenix Axe body spray is
not doing anything for you. We can all
smell you.
>> We do not agree with her. You smell fine
and hair is very purity.
>> Well, I do spend a long time combing it
every morning.
>> People who mock or judge others for how
they look often do not understand that
beauty is within. I personality think
it's cruel to make fun of someone for
how they might look or smell because you
don't always know what they are going
through. Ponies are like birthday
presents. The wrapping paper on the
outside might look nice, but you won't
exactly know what's in there until you
open it up. By the way, I don't know if
you noticed, but there is a black pony
standing beside you. Watch her so she
doesn't steal my [__]
>> You don't want to go in there. I just
pooped and the smell might legitimately
kill you. Don't you ignore me, [__]
>> Excuse me. I'm experiencing a very
urgent biological situation that
requires immediate attention.
>> Oh, so now you can't even acknowledge
the great and powerful Trixie.
>> I'm afraid when the bladder reaches a
certain threshold of internal pressure,
verbal responses become secondary. It
was not my intention to ignore you.
Hey Trixie, I made us all some pot
stickers.
>> Teleporting now? Really? You think it's
funny making me think your magic is
better?
>> Teleporting?
I have no idea what you're talking
about. By the way, I recorded sounds of
Ponyville to play on loop in case we got
home sick this weekend.
>> This is the police. Come out with your
hands up. Get up.
>> Do you want some of my ramen?
>> There is no need for the great and
powerful Trixie is going home where an
egg roll doesn't cost eight freaking
dollars.
>> Trixie.
Mary, I'm here with Starlight as
friends. Of course, you know, just
friends.
Marionette, why are you out of the room?
I only stepped out for a minute. It
didn't seem like a big deal. Oh my god.
No, babe. It's totally a big deal. I
mean, I paid for this trip. Kind of
feels like if you wander off, you should
at least let me know, right? It makes
things easier for the both of us. I've
been holed up in there for hours. And
since I am so generous, I'm willing to
let it slide. You're lucky I'm so
patient. Most ponies wouldn't deal with
someone who just wanders off like you
do. It was only a few minutes. And in
those few minutes, anything could
happen. You could get lost, hurt, and we
don't want that, do we?
>> I guess not.
Twilight.
Oh dear. Looks like there's trouble in
paradise. I wonder who that girl she's
with. Got to say that's quite the
upgrade from you, Trixie. Oh, but she
obviously doesn't hold a candle to you,
my adorable little doll. Come on, let's
go back to the room and you may be
gifted the privilege of massaging my
feet.
Lather it up, [__] I want that [__] so
spotless you'll see your reflection on
it when I step on you. There isn't any
more lotion left.
>> Well, I guess it can't be helped. We
both know what needs to be done then.
Spit. Spit on my feet, Mary. Then lick
between my toes, you dirty little dog.
>> I can just go down to the front desk.
>> Spit on my feet, Mary.
>> Look, mama. It's the laughing Buddha
statue.
>> That's not the laughing Buddha statue,
dear. That's just a fat, balding,
middle-aged pony.
>> Trixie, look, dumplings. Now I'm talking
with my mouth full. I'm being funny.
Trixie, what's the matter? Tell mama
what's wrong, baby. Open up to mama.
>> Twilight, do you even love me anymore?
>> Of course, mama loves her baby. If
anything, baby been avoiding mama.
What the hell is wrong with you?
>> Me? You've been cheating on me this
whole time. I have been nothing but
faithful to you.
>> Lies. All lies. I saw you with with that
sunset shimmer.
>> Sunset shimmer? Are you for real? I
don't know what
I don't know what you think you saw, but
I promise I would never do anything to
hurt you. I love you and you know that.
>> I thought I did. Just like how I thought
the studio JC Staff would never betray
the One Punch Man fan base when they
promised to animated for season 3, yet
here we stand. How dare you compare me
to JC Staff? I'll kill you.
Stop it. You two love each other.
>> Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
>> Who the hell are you?
>> I've been watching you for a while now.
That's creepy.
>> You're both angry because you res
scared.
>> The great and powerful Trixie fears
nothing.
>> Yes, you do. You're scared of losing
each other. And instead of admitting
that, you're fighting. If you truly love
each other, you wouldn't be hurting each
other. You would just walk away.
>> I just didn't think she wanted me
anymore. And I didn't think you trusted
me at all.
>> Then that is what you need to talk
about. Best friends shouldn't be
fighting on Valentine's Day.
>> I got a better idea. How about you mind
your own business, [__]
>> Yeah, [__] Shut up,
>> man. Those two are so toxic. Couldn't be
us. Damn, I got a fart out of my ass.
Put that back on before the smell goes
away, [__] Okay, tamers 1 2 3 4 5 or
just tamers. Can I call you tamers?
Because I feel like if you get to decide
my entire existence, I should at least
get to complain about it. What is my
role here, [__] Seriously, what am I
supposed to be learning? Because every
episode it's the same thing. And before
you say it, yeah, I get it. People
expect it, but you ever think maybe I
don't want someone to fart in my face? I
mean, come on. You already burned my
face off. Like, when was the last time
something good happened to me? You don't
even have to change the whole show. just
like let me breathe once in a while.
Anyway, you're probably not listening.
The scene's probably going to get cut
anyway. You're kind of a [__] like
that.
Uh,
>> pace yourself, sweetie Bell. Remember,
only half slices this week. We don't
have the money for each of us to eat
whole slices of bread.
>> When are you going to become a
financially successful clothing
designer? I'm so hungry.
>> You'll eat whatever I give you, little
queer.
>> Rarity, my friend, may I order room
service from your room? I would use
mine, but I don't want the ponies down
in the lobby to think I'm a fat person.
>> Okay, Fluttershy.
Hey, can I get like two buckets of
orange chicken? What do you mean you
don't have orange chicken? Well, go to
Panda Express and get it. What do you
mean you won't do that? I'm paying $110
to stay here. What else do you have
then? Now you listen here you Ching
Chong ping pong son of a [__] I don't
want spring rolls. I want orange chicken
and a Coca-Cola. No, you are the one who
is the [__] You can't talk to me like
that. I am a Chinese person. Hey Rarity,
I'm not going to get room service after
all. Okay, Fluttershy.
>> Oh. Oh. Uh, hey Mary, don't worry. I'm
getting off next floor, so you won't
have to deal with me long.
Okay, that happened. But I'm not upset.
I understand close physical proximity to
men can be triggering for you,
Marionette.
I'm not going to retaliate because I
respect women and I want you to feel
Okay, now you're just being an [__]
>> You're filming this
>> and what are you going to do about it,
[__]
>> I've seen this before. You're trying to
bait me. You want me to hit back so you
can post it and make us men look bad?
You're just a couple of lousy [__]
You can't say that word.
>> [__] could be a unisex term, too.
>> Uh, no, it really can't. The word [__]
was specifically created to target
women, and when men use it against
women, it's sexist.
>> That is it.
>> Oh, Starlight, get me out of here.
>> Shining armor. How dare you hit a woman?
>> What? No, I She She hit me first.
>> I just don't know what I did wrong.
Frankly, I don't care what she did. You
should know better than to raise a hand
at a lady.
>> Men, am I right? Come on, Swedoms. Let's
go put a bag of frozen peas on your
face.
Wipe that look off your face. I just
feel really relaxed. No, that's the face
of someone replaying something highly
erotic of their own mother in their
head. Twilight, is that you? This place
really is relaxing, isn't it?
The surface ripples are forming near
perfect syosoidal waves. Oh, you've got
to be kidding me. That's it. That's why
she thinks I'm cheating. Wait, who
thinks you're cheating? My wife Trixie,
you married Trixie? Yes, on purpose. Who
are you here with? Sunset Shimmer. And
you didn't do anything weird with her,
right? No, I'm homophobic as [__] But
Trixie tried to talk to me, which I
thought was gross because the Trixie in
the Equestria Girls universe was a cheap
prostitute. So I figured this one was
the same because she tried to touch me
and I ran off so I wouldn't contract
some sort of sexual disease.
I'm going to kill you. What? Why?
Because my wife saw you and now thinks I
cheated. My Valentine's Day was ruined
because of you.
Did you [__] my mom?
>> No, I'm a white guy.
>> I don't know who my dad is, so I'm going
door to door to ask them if they my mom.
>> That's a sad as [__] way to spend
Valentine's Day. Who's your ugly mommy?
>> Chrysalis.
>> Shiny. Who's at the door?
>> It's no one's sweetheart.
>> My mom hates me.
>> Look, kid. I think you should go. It's
not a good look for a 42-year-old public
official to be caught with some random
16-year-old black girl in a Japanese
bath house hotel room on Valentine's
Day. Can't you like go play Club Penguin
or something?
What was that?
>> It's my shot collar. My mom makes me
wear it so she can shock me during
random parts of the day for fun. You
know, you were the first guy today that
didn't call me a nick.
>> Yeah, I try not to show my racism as a
public official. though you are making
it extraordinarily difficult today.
>> May I read you some scriptures?
>> A black Christian Jesus Christ. Look,
there's some handicapped kids your age.
I'm sure they come from dysfunctional
families, too. Why don't you go eat a
watermelon and drink grape soda with
them?
>> Why did you tell Flawless she was
pretty? Because if I told her the truth
that she is the ugliest creature to
grace the earth should alter her
appearance. It is imperative that she
remains as she is.
Indeed. Before she came along, we were
the targets of victimization at school.
Now we are the ones in power.
>> How mean. Those three ponies aren't kind
at all. They're just a group of bullies.
I have to tell Flawless.
>> Someone is listening.
How much did you care?
>> I heard enough to know that you are a
[__]
>> She heard everything. Get her.
Take the [__] outside and tie her to a
real big bottle rocket. When the
fireworks go off tonight, she dies.
>> Holy [__] Apple Bloom. Changeling drone
13,420
is being kidnapped again. Let's go find
a telephone so we can call the cops.
We'll tell them she's white so they
actually come this time.
>> There's two more over here.
Run away scoots.
She's calling for help.
>> We are so cooked.
>> It is done. Let us return home to
Ponyville and watch the Yukobi fighter
on my leap frog tablet.
>> Let my friends go right now.
>> Oh, yeah. And what will you do if we
don't?
>> If you don't, I'll destroy you.
>> Indeed, you could destroy us. You're
more than powerful enough. But if you
did that, you would be wasting precious
time to precure your allies saved. Are
you willing to condemn your friends to
certain death? What's more important to
you? Flawless, revenge or friendship?
>> Forget about us and have your revenge.
Flawless. She made fun of your haircut.
>> Um, you forgot about me.
>> Flawless. You did it. You saved us. I
didn't think you would. Because
>> Because why? Well, I wasn't sure if we
were friends or not,
>> especially since we exclude you from so
many games at school.
>> Ah, shucks, you crazy bastards. Of
course, we're friends.
Now you owe me. Get me a [__] ton of Dr.
Pepper.
Sparkle, why are there two of you? Am I
seeing double through my tears?
>> Trixie, listen. You didn't see me
teleporting around the place. You saw
her. She's me from a separate universe
to ours. Another universe. So, like,
there's another me, too.
>> Not anymore. Her life sucked so bad. She
just rage quit reality a few days ago.
That's why me and Sunset Shimmer are
here celebrating because everyone hated
her.
>> So, that wasn't Twilight. Oh, Twilight,
I should have trusted you. No, this day
started badly because I hurt you first
when I didn't take your career as a
street magician seriously. Going from
cheap sex work to being a failed street
magician already made Trixie feel like a
joke sometimes, but hearing it from you
sparkle, that that really hurt me. I
love that you go out there and perform
no matter how many ponies show up.
>> Yeah, three. And I bet those three
ponies get the best damn show of their
lives.
Trixie sure is tired.
>> Hey. Um, Trixie,
>> what is it?
>> You do know that I didn't fall in love
with you because you can or can't afford
things.
>> Sure, Trixie knows that. Though Trixie
is sure you could do way better than her
if you really wanted.
>> No way. There will never be anyone
better than you. Twilight
for you and you can dream.
I believe I will love to you forever
when you are let me know I will let it
run away
and if I dream it away I
know more
baby kiss me kiss me my love kiss me
kiss
like no other
goodbye
for a while.
Kiss me, kiss me till the morning. It's
never stop
you.
Touch me with your finger.
I can get enough about you, baby. I know
you're so pretty. It's a break.
Can I let you
find a way? And if I'm dreaming, I want
to make I
know more.
Hold me, baby. Kiss me, kiss me, my
love. Kiss me, kiss me like no other. I
can't say goodbye.
before
you stay till the morning
and know I'm you.
I believe I will love to you forever.
I won't let it be. I want to find a way.
And if I'm dreaming, I walk away.
I've been long before, but now it's even
more.
Come home, baby. Kiss me, kiss me, my
love. Kiss me, kiss me like no other.
Goodbye.
Kiss me, kiss me till the morning. Kiss
me, kiss me. Never stop.
I love you and you can dream.
Touch me with your tears.
I can't get enough about you, baby. I
know you're so pretty. It's the rain.
Can I let you go? Now we're ready to
find a way. And if I'm dreaming, I want